<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-10-15T22:10:41+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost//</id><title type="html">Constellar</title><subtitle>A team formed in 2017 to innovate.</subtitle><author><name>Constellar</name></author><entry><title type="html">Our Mindmap</title><link href="http://localhost//2017/10/15/Our-Mindmap.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our Mindmap" /><published>2017-10-15T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-10-15T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost//2017/10/15/Our-Mindmap</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost//2017/10/15/Our-Mindmap.html">&lt;iframe class=&quot;pdf&quot; id=&quot;mindmap&quot; src=&quot;/pdf.js/viewer.html?file=/pdf/mindmap.pdf&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download: &lt;a href=&quot;/pdf/mindmap.pdf&quot;&gt;mindmap.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Constellar</name></author><category term="team" /><summary type="html">Download: mindmap.pdf</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Datapack</title><link href="http://localhost//2017/10/15/Datapack.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Datapack" /><published>2017-10-15T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-10-15T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost//2017/10/15/Datapack</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost//2017/10/15/Datapack.html">&lt;iframe class=&quot;pdf&quot; id=&quot;mindmap&quot; src=&quot;/pdf.js/viewer.html?file=/pdf/datapack.pdf&quot; width=&quot;339&quot; height=&quot;190&quot; /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download: &lt;a href=&quot;/pdf/datapack.pdf&quot;&gt;mindmap.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Constellar</name></author><category term="team" /><summary type="html">Download: mindmap.pdf</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Thoughts on Underground</title><link href="http://localhost//2017/10/09/Thoughts-on-Underground.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thoughts on Underground" /><published>2017-10-09T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-10-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost//2017/10/09/Thoughts-on-Underground</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost//2017/10/09/Thoughts-on-Underground.html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The topic is “The plan to design the direction sign in the underground car park in our school”, which is very close to our campus life. I gave this topic to my team members and after discussion we concluded that this might be best over the several topics raised by the team. The topic was originated during my unpleasant experience in the underground car park when I planned to come back to the dormitory and I got lost. It took me a long time to go back to the ground and finally reach the destination. Therefore, I began to think that I can’t be the first to feel puzzled in the underground, and the signals in it is not detailed enough for me to find the right way. Hence, re-designing the signals in the park must be a meaningful and helpful item.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The location of the signals.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–Jack R. Liu, 刘润&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The school is designed with a complete underground transit system. It is quite useful in bad weather if one does not want to walk in a heavy shower, in which holding an umbrella barely do something useful. However as it sits this system is poorly documented and is considered a maze by the majority. I think making this awesome yet seldom used feature understood by all of us worth some hard work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–Jim Wang, 王锦瑞&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;我们的课题是关于学校地下车库的路标建设，之所以选择这个，一是因为车库就在我们脚底下，和我们的生活很贴近，我们能够有充足的机会去研究。二来也是因为学校的地下车库非常大，稍微深入下就容易在其中迷路，若是车停在车库里面，在没有路标的指引下，不熟悉场地的驾驶员需要花大量的时间去寻找出口，十分麻烦。如何让人能够快速的了解地下车库，并顺利的没有障碍的从中走出，就显得很有必要。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;在这个研究课题中，我最感兴趣的是如何增加指引的多样性。我们的课题可能也不一定要局限在单纯的路标建设上，还可以对地下车库进行一定的充分利用，在完成的基础上我们还可以勘察一下地下车库，然后思考如何利用并进行指引。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–章烨昊&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;学校地下停车场的设置复杂，对于外来的客人，在停车场现有的有限的图标下，很难在短时间内不绕路的走出地下停车场。这个问题给来客造成了烦恼，也不利于学校形象的树立。我认为这个问题亟需解决。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;主要是地下停车场的标志设置与信息给予，通过在合适的位置安装提示标志，对出场车辆进行有效地引导。以达到让车辆快速出场，并按照不同路线实施分流，防止地下停车场堵塞的目的。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–陆启明&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;自己对方向本来就很不敏感，在地下较为黑暗和压抑的情况下就更不知所措。所以，对于我以后开车停车来说，能够不在地下室里迷路就非常重要。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;地向停车场面积一般非常大，路很绕，但是指示具体区域的路牌很少接近没有，所以非常容易迷路。而且即使显示在什么区域有停车位，但是还是因为区域面积大，不能及时找到，所以在闷热的地下环境中焦头烂额。研究地下停车场可以让我们研究出合理的路牌来快速了解地下车库的排布，得知车位信息和停车情况。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–邱源&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Constellar</name></author><category term="team" /><summary type="html">The topic is “The plan to design the direction sign in the underground car park in our school”, which is very close to our campus life. I gave this topic to my team members and after discussion we concluded that this might be best over the several topics raised by the team. The topic was originated during my unpleasant experience in the underground car park when I planned to come back to the dormitory and I got lost. It took me a long time to go back to the ground and finally reach the destination. Therefore, I began to think that I can’t be the first to feel puzzled in the underground, and the signals in it is not detailed enough for me to find the right way. Hence, re-designing the signals in the park must be a meaningful and helpful item. The location of the signals. –Jack R. Liu, 刘润 The school is designed with a complete underground transit system. It is quite useful in bad weather if one does not want to walk in a heavy shower, in which holding an umbrella barely do something useful. However as it sits this system is poorly documented and is considered a maze by the majority. I think making this awesome yet seldom used feature understood by all of us worth some hard work. –Jim Wang, 王锦瑞 我们的课题是关于学校地下车库的路标建设，之所以选择这个，一是因为车库就在我们脚底下，和我们的生活很贴近，我们能够有充足的机会去研究。二来也是因为学校的地下车库非常大，稍微深入下就容易在其中迷路，若是车停在车库里面，在没有路标的指引下，不熟悉场地的驾驶员需要花大量的时间去寻找出口，十分麻烦。如何让人能够快速的了解地下车库，并顺利的没有障碍的从中走出，就显得很有必要。 在这个研究课题中，我最感兴趣的是如何增加指引的多样性。我们的课题可能也不一定要局限在单纯的路标建设上，还可以对地下车库进行一定的充分利用，在完成的基础上我们还可以勘察一下地下车库，然后思考如何利用并进行指引。 –章烨昊 学校地下停车场的设置复杂，对于外来的客人，在停车场现有的有限的图标下，很难在短时间内不绕路的走出地下停车场。这个问题给来客造成了烦恼，也不利于学校形象的树立。我认为这个问题亟需解决。 主要是地下停车场的标志设置与信息给予，通过在合适的位置安装提示标志，对出场车辆进行有效地引导。以达到让车辆快速出场，并按照不同路线实施分流，防止地下停车场堵塞的目的。 –陆启明 自己对方向本来就很不敏感，在地下较为黑暗和压抑的情况下就更不知所措。所以，对于我以后开车停车来说，能够不在地下室里迷路就非常重要。 地向停车场面积一般非常大，路很绕，但是指示具体区域的路牌很少接近没有，所以非常容易迷路。而且即使显示在什么区域有停车位，但是还是因为区域面积大，不能及时找到，所以在闷热的地下环境中焦头烂额。研究地下停车场可以让我们研究出合理的路牌来快速了解地下车库的排布，得知车位信息和停车情况。 –邱源</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Our mission</title><link href="http://localhost//2017/10/09/The-Mission.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our mission" /><published>2017-10-09T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-10-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost//2017/10/09/The-Mission</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost//2017/10/09/The-Mission.html">&lt;p&gt;After a heated discussion we decided to add signs to the underground car park to show people the direction. This should resolve the issue, and while this seems to be a trivial task, it actually takes more than just printing some signs and put them up in the wall. We also need it to&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Constellar</name></author><category term="team" /><summary type="html">After a heated discussion we decided to add signs to the underground car park to show people the direction. This should resolve the issue, and while this seems to be a trivial task, it actually takes more than just printing some signs and put them up in the wall. We also need it to</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Team Norms</title><link href="http://localhost//2017/09/27/Team-Norms.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Team Norms" /><published>2017-09-27T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-09-27T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost//2017/09/27/Team-Norms</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost//2017/09/27/Team-Norms.html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Respect one another.
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Respect others’ ideas and opinions, attacking others in any ways is banned.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Respect others’ speaking, do not interrupt others.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Respect others’ work, laughing at poor works is banned.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Respect others’ private life.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work effectively and efficiently.
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;No chatting on subjects that has no link to the work.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Participate in the topic and brainstorming actively.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Always be careful and focused on what you do.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Think different&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Think critically.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Doubt the assumptions.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Everyone should express his own opinion.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Time should be well planned.
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Control the time of every part in case time is not enough finally.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Have a try bravely, act undoubtfully.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Safety and Happiness is No.1 priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Signee (in alphabetic order): Jack R. Liu, Qiming Lu, Daisy Qiu, Jim Wang, Yehao Zhang.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Constellar</name></author><category term="team" /><summary type="html">Respect one another. Respect others’ ideas and opinions, attacking others in any ways is banned. Respect others’ speaking, do not interrupt others. Respect others’ work, laughing at poor works is banned. Respect others’ private life. Work effectively and efficiently. No chatting on subjects that has no link to the work. Participate in the topic and brainstorming actively. Always be careful and focused on what you do. Think different Think critically. Doubt the assumptions. Everyone should express his own opinion. Time should be well planned. Control the time of every part in case time is not enough finally. Have a try bravely, act undoubtfully. Safety and Happiness is No.1 priority. Signee (in alphabetic order): Jack R. Liu, Qiming Lu, Daisy Qiu, Jim Wang, Yehao Zhang.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Epoch</title><link href="http://localhost//2017/09/27/Epoch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Epoch" /><published>2017-09-27T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2017-09-27T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost//2017/09/27/Epoch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost//2017/09/27/Epoch.html">&lt;p&gt;Site is online. Hope we can put up some real content - not another hello world - before the sun sets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;road-map&quot;&gt;Road map&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finish all the style thing. We can’t have a team blog named Hydeout.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Give our team a fancy name. We aren’t No.2 all the days.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As said above, put up some real content, probably that team norms? Not very sure if what we should go for though.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Constellar</name></author><category term="misc" /><summary type="html">Site is online. Hope we can put up some real content - not another hello world - before the sun sets. Road map Finish all the style thing. We can’t have a team blog named Hydeout. Give our team a fancy name. We aren’t No.2 all the days. As said above, put up some real content, probably that team norms? Not very sure if what we should go for though.</summary></entry></feed>